maxstudio.com 2018-02-25

# Privacy

Leon Max, Inc (“MAX STUDIO”“we” or “us”) is committed to protecting the privacy of the users, visitors, customers and subscribers with regards to the maxstudio.com website (the "Website") and any affiliated websites and entities. By accessing or using this website, applications or other MAX STUDIO product, internet presence or service on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, console or other device (collectively, "Device"), you consent to our Privacy Policy. MAX STUDIO may modify this Privacy Policy at any time effective upon its posting. Your continued use of our products and services constitutes your acceptance to this Privacy Policy and any updates. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and is subject to, the Terms of Use.

The servers that make the website available and store the information that is collected on or through the website may be located in the United States of America ("USA"). If you are located outside the USA, please note that the information you provide will be transferred to the USA. The laws of the USA may not provide the same level of legal data protection as the country from which you access the website. By using the website and submitting personal information to us, you consent to and authorize such transfers and the use and processing by us of information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" is personally identifiable information about an individual person including, but not limited to, a person's name, physical address, e-mail address, and telephone number, as more particularly described under applicable U.S. privacy laws.

**I. Collected Information** _  
_

**What Information You Give MAX STUDIO  
** We collect information you give us or permit us to access. Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, image, birth date, email and physical address, telephone number, gender, contact lists, social media information and profile, location (GPS) information, activity and performance information, and when necessary, credit card information.  

**What Information MAX STUDIO Collects From You**  
We may automatically collect information regarding your interaction with, and use of our products, services and any affiliated websites and entities. Information we may collect includes, but is not limited to, your telephone number, Device identifier and hardware information, IP address, browser type and language, cookie information, system type, whether you have enabling software to access certain features, access times, referring website URLs, information about your purchases and other information about your interactions with us.

**What We Collect From other MAX STUDIO Interactions, Affiliates, Associated Entities and Third Parties**  
We may combine information you give us with other information from MAX STUDIO sources, transactions and communications. This may include, but is not limited to, information from MAX STUDIO Wholesale stores, trunk shows, direct mail, catalogs, events, products and applications, or other interactions.  We may also combine that information with data that is publicly available and data from third parties. We also collect information about gift recipients provided by the giver.

**Use of Cookies  
** Cookies are alphanumeric (letter and numeric) identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and provide features that help your user experience. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to manage cookies or disable them altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of features on maxstudio.com and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Children's Privacy  
** This website is a general audience website and is not directed for use by children. We do not intend to collect personal information from anyone who is under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 you should not provide any personal information to us and you should use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Use of Information  
** We may use your personal information to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, and to provide customer service. Your information also may be used to contact you about sales, new products, special offers, new site features and to enhance your MAX STUDIO experience, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications. Your information may also be utilized to analyze user behavior and trends. For marketing and promotional purposes, your information may be used to communicate regarding contest, surveys, events, and to display relevant marketing to you. The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from companies affiliated with MAX STUDIO and from other companies. Aggregating data allows us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide you with product recommendations and special offers.

**II. Information Sharing**  
**_  
_ MAX STUDIO and Affiliated Parties**  
Information retrieved on maxstudio.com may be relayed to LEON MAX, INC companies and affiliates, some of which may be outside the U.S.  

**Service Providers**  
We may transfer your information to MAX STUDIO service providers to conduct our business. For example, they may handle credit card processing, shipping, data management, email distribution, market research, information analysis, and promotions management. We may also share your information to administer features.

**By Law or to Protect Rights**  
We may disclose information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, to enforce our policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property or safety. We may share information to prevent illegal uses of MAX STUDIO products and services or violations of the terms of use or to defend ourselves against third-party claims. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation.

**__Business Transfers**  
Your information may be transferred to a third party as a part of our business assets in a sale of a part or all of MAX STUDIO.  If this should happen, notice will be provided by posting to the website or other form of communication.

**III. Public Sharing**  
**_  
_  
Default Sharing**  
When you join or use certain services, you agree to publicly share a basic amount of information, which may include your username, city location, and profile picture.  

**Sharing You Choose**  
You may choose to share certain information. In order to participate in certain features, you may have to adjust your privacy settings and share more information. You may also choose to share your activity on other platforms, such as but not limited to Facebook and Twitter. Please read the privacy policies of those platforms, because your MAX STUDIO activity that is published on those platforms will no longer be governed by MAX STUDIO's privacy policy.

**MAX STUDIO Sharing**  
Information that is publicly shared may be used by MAX STUDIO for promotional purposes.

**Protecting Information – Security Measures**   
We use a variety of security measures, including encryption and authentication tools, to help protect your information. We use secure servers when you place orders. All credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted within our databases.

**No Guarantee**  
Like other companies, MAX STUDIO cannot guarantee 100% the security or confidentiality of the information you provide to us.  
 **  
Communication/Unsubscribe/Opt-Out  
** Regardless of the settings you select, MAX STUDIO may send you service-related communications.  To unsubscribe and stop receiving messages, please change your settings or follow the instructions in the email, text message, notification or other message type.  If you have unsubscribed from any MAX STUDIO communications, due to production schedules, you may receive communications already in production.

**International Users  
** Our digital operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of your location, you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed and stored in the United States, and allow MAX STUDIO to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Terms of Use  
** Your use of our products and services, and any disputes arising from them, is subject to this Privacy Policy.

For questions or concerns, please email MAX STUDIO Consumer Services/Privacy at service@maxstudioservices.com or write to us at the following address:

LEON MAX, INC  
dba MAX STUDIO  
Attn: Director of eCommerce Services  
3100 New York Drive  
Pasadena, CA 91107
